{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20was%20the%20first%20President%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F",
      "correct_answer": "George%20Washington",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Thomas%20Jefferson",
        "John%20Adams",
        "Abraham%20Lincoln"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20event%20marked%20the%20beginning%20of%20the%20American%20Revolutionary%20War%3F",
      "correct_answer": "The%20Battle%20of%20Lexington%20and%20Concord",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The%20Boston%20Tea%20Party",
        "The%20Signing%20of%20the%20Declaration%20of%20Independence",
        "The%20Boston%20Massacre"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20Amendment%20to%20the%20United%20States%20Constitution%20gave%20women%20the%20right%20to%20vote%3F",
      "correct_answer": "19th%20Amendment",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "15th%20Amendment",
        "21st%20Amendment",
        "18th%20Amendment"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20ship%20that%20brought%20the%20Pilgrims%20to%20America%20in%201620%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Mayflower",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Santa%20Maria",
        "Nina",
        "Discovery"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20was%20the%20author%20of%20the%20Declaration%20of%20Independence%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Thomas%20Jefferson",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "George%20Washington",
        "Benjamin%20Franklin",
        "John%20Adams"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20president%20was%20in%20office%20during%20the%20Great%20Depression%20and%20World%20War%20II%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Franklin%20D.%20Roosevelt",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Herbert%20Hoover",
        "Harry%20S.%20Truman",
        "Dwight%20D.%20Eisenhower"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20was%20the%20president%20of%20the%20Confederate%20States%20of%20America%20during%20the%20American%20Civil%20War%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Jefferson%20Davis",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Robert%20E.%20Lee",
        "Abraham%20Lincoln",
        "Ulysses%20S.%20Grant"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20president%20is%20famously%20known%20for%20the%20Monroe%20Doctrine%3F",
      "correct_answer": "James%20Monroe",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "James%20Madison",
        "John%20Adams",
        "Thomas%20Jefferson"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20was%20the%20first%20African%20American%20elected%20President%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Barack%20Obama",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Joe%20Biden",
        "Donald%20Trump",
        "George%20W.%20Bush"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20act%20signed%20by%20President%20Andrew%20Jackson%20forced%20the%20removal%20of%20Native%20Americans%20from%20their%20lands%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Indian%20Removal%20Act",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Trail%20of%20Tears%20Act",
        "Native%20American%20Resettlement%20Act",
        "Cherokee%20Removal%20Act"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
